let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the birth date of Prophet Muhammad?",
        answer: "562 AD",
        options: [
            "600 AD",
            "562 AD",
            "555 AD",
            "720 AD"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the significance of the city of Mecca in Prophet Muhammad’s life?",
        answer: "It is where he was born and started his prophetic mission.",
        options: [
            "It is where he was born and started his prophetic mission.",
            "It is where he migrated to escape persecution.",
            "It is where he received his first revelation",
            "It is where he wrote the Quran."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who was the first wife of Prophet Muhammad?",
        answer: "Khadija bint Khuwaylid",
        options: [
            " Aisha bint Abi Bakr",
            "Khadija bint Khuwaylid",
            "Sawda bint Zam’a",
            "Hafsa bint Umar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the significance of the Hijra in the life of Prophet Muhammad?",
        answer: "It marks his journey from Mecca to Medina.",
        options: [
            "It marks his journey from Medina to Mecca.",
            "It marks his journey from Medina to Jerusalem.",
            "It marks his journey from Mecca to Jerusalem.",
            "It marks his journey from Mecca to Medina."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the full name of Prophet Muhammed?",
        answer: "Muhammad ibn Abdullah ibn Abdul-Muttalib",
        options: [
            "Muhammad ibn Ali ibn Abu Talib",
            "Muhammad ibn Umar ibn Khattab",
            "Muhammad ibn Abu Bakr ibn Uthman",
            "Muhammad ibn Abdullah ibn Abdul-Muttalib"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What was the name of Prophet Muhammad’s nursing mother?",
        answer: "Halimah bint Abi Dhuayb",
        options: [
            " Khadijah bint Khuwaylid",
            "Amina bint Wahb",
            "Fatimah bint Muhammad",
            "Halimah bint Abi Dhuayb"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which one of those is Prophet Muhammad's son?",
        answer: "Qasim",
        options: [
            "Qasim",
            "Mohamed",
            "Issa",
            "Hussein"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What was the first war of Prophet Muhammed?",
        answer: "Battle of Badr",
        options: [
            "Battle of Uhud",
            "Battle of the Trench",
            "Battle of Badr",
            "Conquest of Mecca"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How old was the prophet when the revelation came down on him?",
        answer: "40 years old",
        options: [
            "23 years old",
            "40 years old",
            "63 years old",
            "43 years old"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "When did the Conquest of Mecca took place?",
        answer: "8th hijri",
        options: [
            "8th hijri",
            "12 hijri",
            "6 hijri",
            "9 hijri"
        ]
    }
];
